in this video we'll go over how to
在此视频中，我们将介绍如何初始化银行讲师如何赢得
initialize Bank instructors win a
contract and heads from multiple pen
合同和多个笔合同的负责人，我们将首先探讨如何
contracts first we'll go over how to
call pan constructors in solidity
实体构造函数中的call pan构造函数始终在
constructors are always executed in a
certain order so you'll go through some
特定顺序，因此您将通过一些示例来了解该顺序是什么
examples and find out what that order is
and lastly you cannot override a state
最后，您不能覆盖父合同中声明的状态变量
variable declared in a parent contract
by simply reading it in a child contract
通过简单地在子合同中阅读它，所以我将向您展示如何
so I'll show you an example of how to
correctly override a state variable that
正确覆盖首先在父合同中声明的状态变量
was declared in a parent contract first
let's step back and review how to call a
让我们退后一步，回顾一下如何调用单亲构造函数。
single parent constructor here we have a
contract named X and we'll use this as a
名为X的合同，我们将其用作其他合同的基本合同，以
base contract for other contracts to
inherit from from a child contract we'll
从子合同继承，我们将一个字符串传递给
pass in a string to the constructor of
contract X and save that string in the
合约X并将该字符串保存在状态变量名称中，这里我们有
state variable name here we have
contract B that adds from contract X and
从合约X添加的合约B和一种传递参数以追加的方式
one way to pass parameters to append
constructor is like this and another way
构造函数就是这样，另一种方式是像
is to calling the parent contract like a
function next to the constructor of the
子合同的构造函数旁边的函数，您还可以传递一个
child contract and you can also pass a
variable input to a parent constructor
像这样的例子，输入到父构造函数的变量类似于
like this this example is similar to the
example above here we're passing in a
在上面的示例中，我们将固定输入传递给父合约
fixed input to the parent contract
whereas here we're passing in a variable
而在这里，我们传递一个变量输入，接下来让我们看一下如何调用
input next let's go over how to call
parent constructors when a contract has
父构造函数当一个合同有许多父合同时，我们将创建一个
many parent contracts we'll create a
parent contract named Y and declare
名为Y的父合约并向存储字符串声明状态变量
state variable to a storage string we
don't want the state variable to
不想状态变量覆盖内部的状态变量
override the state variable inside
contract X so we will name it
合约X，所以我们将其命名为不同
differently
call text and if you want to call the
调用文本，如果您想调用构造函数或多个父代，这是
constructors or several parents this is
one way to do it another way is to call
一种方法是在内部调用父构造函数
the parent constructor inside the
constructor of the child contract here
子合同的构造函数在这里，我们不在父母之间插入逗号
we don't put commas in between parent
contracts and this is how you pass
合同，这就是您将变量传递给父级的方式
variables to parent
jug's the syntax is similar to the
水罐的语法类似于上面的示例，除了这里我们要传递
example above except here we're passing
in fixed input whereas here we're
在固定输入中，而在这里我们将游戏变量传递给配对
passing game variables to pair
constructors and you can pass different
构造函数，您可以将不同的参数传递给父构造函数
parameters to the parent constructors
like this here the constructor of
像这样，合同D的构造函数接受两个输入name和
contract D takes in two inputs name and
text and it passes the name variable to
文本，并将名称变量传递给父合约X并传递文本
parent contract X and passes the text
variable to a parent contract Y let's
将变量分配给父合同Y让我们部署此合同并验证
deploy this contract and verify that the
state variable for contract X and
合约X和合约的状态变量为什么我将变量设置为
contract why I set to the variables that
we pass in to the constructor of
我们传递给合同II的构造者编译和部署合同
contract II compile and deploy contract
D I'm going to pass in the string food
D我将传递字符串食物作为第一个参数，并输入bar作为
for the first parameter and bar for the
second parameter once the contract is
部署合同后，您可以验证是否调用了第二个参数
deployed you can verify that calling the
state variable name returns the string
状态变量名称返回字符串foo并调用状态变量文本
foo and calling the state variable text
returns a string bar so I just showed
返回一个字符串条，所以我只是向您展示了三种调用的构造函数的方法
you three ways to call constructors of
parent contracts next that's what do
父合同接下来是什么，将显示一些示例
some examples that will show in what
water parent constructors are called we
水父构造函数被称为我们希望能够看到顺序
want to be able to see the order in
which the pen constructors are called so
笔构造函数被调用的原因，所以首先让我们在内部创建一个事件
first let's create an event inside
contract X and fire that event when the
合约X并在调用构造函数时触发该事件
constructor is called
and we'll do something similar for
我们将对合同Y进行类似的操作接下来，我们将创建两个
contract Y as well next we'll create two
contracts that both in here from the pen
来自笔合约X＆Y的合约
contract X&Y
you
你
looking at the constructor for culture D
看文化D的构造函数，看起来父合约X是
it looks like the parent contract X is
called before the pen contract Y and for
在笔合约Y之前调用，对于合约F的构造函数，它看起来像
the constructor of contract F it looks
like the pen contact Y is called before
就像在您调用笔合约x之前先调用笔联系人Y
the pen contract x is called when you
deploy contract e inside the transaction
在交易日志中部署合同e，您会看到构造函数X
log you'll see that the constructor X
was called and then the constructor
被调用，然后在调用我时以及在部署时构造函数
while I was called and when you deployed
contract F you will see that the
合约F，您会看到调用了构造函数X，然后
constructor X was called and then the
constructor Y was called even though
即使在这里我们按Y的顺序列出它，也调用了构造函数Y
here we have it listed in order from Y
to X so in summary the order in which
到X，因此总之，笔构造函数的调用顺序为
the pen constructors are called is
determined by the inheritance and not by
由继承而不是由父级的顺序确定
the order in which the parent
constructors are called next let's see
接下来调用构造函数，让我们看一个如何覆盖状态的示例
an example of how to override a state
variable in a parent contract in a wrong
父合同中的变量以错误的方式显示，之后我将向您展示
way and after that I'll show you the
right way to do it first we'll create a
首先正确的方法，我们将创建基本合同并存储地址
base contract and store an address
inside a state variable next we'll
在状态变量中，接下来我们将创建一个引用该函数的函数
create a function that references this
state variable for simplicity we'll just
为了简单起见，我们只返回状态变量的值
return the value of the state variable
next we'll create a child contract that
接下来，我们将创建一个以错误方式从合同继承的子合同
inherits from contract a the wrong way
to override a state variable of a parent
覆盖父合同的状态变量是在
contract is to read eclair it in the
child contract so in this case we try to
子合同，因此在这种情况下，我们尝试覆盖地址状态变量
override the address state variable
declared in a parent contract by V
在父合同中通过V在子合同中声明而声明，以及
declaring it in the child contract and
assigning the different value after you
部署合同B后分配不同的值，您可以在此处注意到
deploy contract B you can notice here
that the value of the state variable is
状态变量的值是在此内部分配的值
the value that was assigned here inside
contract B but calling the function get
合约B，但调用该函数得到的只是返回状态变量，即
a just return the state variable that
was initialized here inside contract a
是在合约内部初始化的，因此此示例表明您无法
so this example shows that you cannot
override a state variable declared in a
覆盖我们在子对象中声明的合同中声明的状态变量
contract by we declared inside a child
contract next let's see the correct way
接下来，让我们看看覆盖状态变量的正确方法
of overriding state variables will
create another contract that also
创建另一个合同，该合同也继承自合同日内的
inherits from contract day inside the
constructor we just override the state
构造函数，我们只是覆盖从继承的状态变量
variable that was inherited from the
parent contract in this case we'll just
在这种情况下，我们只需将地址变量分配给
reassign the address variable to a
different value deploy contract C and
不同的价值部署合同C并调用这两个函数，您可以在此处看到
call the two functions you can see here
that the state variable was set to the
将状态变量设置为合同的构造函数中的值
value inside the constructor of contract
C and calling the function get address
C并调用函数get address也会返回设置的值
also return the value that was set
inside contract C to reiterate if you
如果您想覆盖a的状态变量，请在合同C中进行重申
want to override the state variable of a
parent contract you just reassign it and
父合同，您只需重新分配它，我们就在
we declaring state variable inside the
child contract is a big mistake
个人合同是一个大错误，我个人已将其寄给了错误的人
personally I've sent either to the wrong
digest with this mistake and notice the
消化此错误并注意坚固性不会发出任何警告
solidity does not give off any warnings
for state variables that are we declared
对于我们在此视频中的子合同中声明的状态变量，我们去了
in child contracts in this video we went
over how to call constructors of parent
关于如何调用父合约的构造函数，父构造函数将
contracts parent constructors will
always be called in the order in which
总是按照它们乱扔的顺序而不是按照
they are in garrotted and not in the
order they are called inside the
以便在子合同的构造函数中调用它们，并
constructor of a child contract and to
override the value of a state variable
在父合同中覆盖状态变量的值不要读eclair
in a parent contract don't read eclair
it in the child contract instead just
而是在子合同中将其重新分配，这就是本视频的结尾
reassign it that's the end of this video
any questions or feedback please put
任何问题或反馈，请把它们放在下面的评论中，谢谢您
them in the comments below thank you so
much for watching and have a nice week
很值得看，度过了愉快的一周